<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rising 11</string>
    <string name="title_activity_create_contest">CREATE A CONTEST</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">RISING 11</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_notification">Notification</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="title_activity_temp">TempActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="underline_string"><u>Know more</u></string>
    <string name="line1_bullet">\u2022 Track the status of withdrawals</string>
    <string name="line2_bullet">\u2022 Enjoy access to exciting features &amp; rewards</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <!-- API URLs -->
    <string name="paytm_mid">YfSFky58226330996541</string>
    <string name="generate_checksum_url">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/paytm/generateChecksum.php</string>
    <string name="callback_url">https://pguat.paytm.com/paytmchecksum/paytmCallback.jsp</string>

    <!-- apis-->
    <string name="signup">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/register-user.php</string>
    <string name="signin">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/login.php</string>
    <string name="forgetpass">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/forget-pass.php</string>
    <string name="update_profile">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/update-profile.php</string>

    <string name="verifymobile">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/verify-mobile.php</string>
    <string name="userdetails">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/get-user-details.php</string>
    <string name="wallet">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/get-wallet-balance.php</string>


    <string name="how_it_works_step">Step-1:- Verify your email &amp; mobile no.\n\nStep-2:-Refer your Friend <b>Rising11</b> by unique referral code.
        \n\nStep-3:-When your Friend Register and Verify their email &amp; mobile no. , your friend will get ₹50 instantly and you will get ₹15 cash bonus instantly.
        \n\nStep-4:-when your Friend Verify their pan-card &amp; Bank-account further you will get ₹10 cash bonus.</string>

    <string name="how_it_works_button">***If any user will found to miss-use of cash bonus by creating multiple accounts &amp; verify them by fake documents then it will be considered under fair-play violation.
        \n\n*Please refer Terms &amp; Conditions (Refer &amp; Earn) and Fair-Play Violation.</string>

    <string name="fair_play_rules_top">What are the rules of FairPlay?</string>
    <string name="fair_play_rules_middle">• You cannot create multipe account.
        \n\n• You cannot misuse your invite code in any way.
         \n\n• You cannot misuse your cash bonus in any way.
         \n \n\nWhat happens when:
          \n\n• You misuse your Invite Code by creating multiple account:
         \n\n<b> WE BLOCK THE CASH BONUS AND THE INVITE CODE</b>
         \n\n• You misuse the cash bonus and win multiple contests:
         \n\n<b>WE TAKE BACK WINNING OF THAT CONTEST</b>
    </string>

    <string name="fair_play_TC_1">Rising11 considers Fair Play to be a priority at its platform and any user violating the Fair Play Terms of Rising11 shall be entitled to bear various consequences including Blocking of the user Account.</string>

    <string name="fair_play_TC_2">• The people you are referring should all be genuine accounts and the user should not use any fake accounts to gain the “Refer &amp; Earn” cash bonus amount.
        \n\n• The PAN card of all your referred friends should be verified. In an event, the PAN card of more than 3 of your referred friends are not verified the user will be considered as violating the Fair Play Terms of Rising11.
        \n\n• A user creating more than one account on Rising11 platform will be considered as violating the Fair Play Terms of Rising11 as Rising11 neither allows nor encourages any user to create more than one user account on Rising11.
        \n\n• Withdrawing money by using any unlawful or illegal means or trying to withdraw money by illegal manners is considered as Fair Play violation at Rising11.
        \n\n• If a user is found submitting fake copies or someone else’s documents while registering with Rising11, the act will be considered as violating the Fair Play Terms of Rising11.
        \n\n• In case a user is found to be creating and using multiple accounts on a single device amid regular platform audits, then, the case shall be considered to violate Fair Play Terms of Rising11 and shall attract needed actions. As part of the action, the withdrawal request of the user shall be put on hold.</string>

    <string name="fair_play_TC_3">\n\n• As a part of consequences for violating the terms of Fair Play at Rising11, the account of the user found to be violating the Fair Play terms will be blocked.
        \n\n• Further, in other scenario the total amount present in the Rising11 wallet of the user violating the Fair Play terms of Rising11 will be reduced to zero.</string>


    <!-- CRIC_API -->

    <string name="Cric_APi_Key">1FiCfYXHgZPywU2JFPgdnPL7NX63</string>
    <string name="Cric_cricket_score">https://cricapi.com/api/cricketScore</string>


    <string-array name="sort_by_value">
        <item>Player Type</item>
        <item>Points</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- More Section Data -->

    <string name="help_section_1">For any queries please write email to us on- \n<b>support@rising11.com</b> \n<b>info@rising11.com</b>
        \n\nYou can also message us on WhatsApp at -  <b>7023083083</b>
    </string>

    <string name="fb">https://www.facebook.com/Rising11kk/?ti=as</string>
    <string name="insta">https://www.instagram.com/rising11kk</string>
    <string name="twitter">https://twitter.com/Rising11_kk?s=08</string>
    <string name="youtube">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCMWcWW4oLaTOZGDo1enSpHg</string>


    <string name="jobs">Thanks for being interested to know about us. Well, we are a bunch of Sports lovers who want to present other Sports lovers an experience like never before. We worked day in and day out to come up with this delightful experience of Sports matches. Hence, we would like to invite you to be a part of our fastest growing &amp; promising family
        \n\nCongratulations! We’re now open to invite more members to join our fantasy family.
        \n\nSend your resume to us at - <b>info@rising11.com</b>
        \n\n<b>We look forward to joining hands with you!</b> </string>


    <string name="legality"> Fantasy sports are considered to be a legal practice around the world with certain states being an exception. The fantasy sports are entirely based on the concept of Game of Skills, wherein the users form their own teams and are allocated points on the basis of on-field performance of their chosen players.
The services and Fun Features offered by Rising11 are all a game of skills and do not promote, encourage or support gambling or betting in any manner. The game of skills can be defined as a game wherein the skills of the individuals participating in any online fantasy game play a dominant role rather than the mere luck of the individuals. The individuals in game of skills use their skills, knowledge, training and attention for participation and winning.
Rising11 is completely legal as it offers services, Fun Features, Program(s) and Contest(s) related to fantasy sports. The services, contest(s) and program(s) related to fantasy sports offered by Rising11 enables its users to create their own team of playing XI prior the match begins and then the teams are awarded points on the basis of the real life performance of the players chosen by the users in their playing XI. The individual whose team scores the highest aggregate of points is announced as the winners. The formation of team by the users of Rising11 is entirely dependent on the skills, knowledge and attention of the users which makes the fantasy sports offered at Rising11 a game of skills and 100% legal.
ALIGNMENT WITH THE INDIAN LAWS
The game of skills such as the fantasy sports gamings are considered to be legal all over India expect certain states such as Assam, Odisha, Telangana and Nagaland.
The PGA defines the act of “public gambling” and keeping of a common gaming house as a criminal and punishable act in India. The Public Gambling Act, 1867 (“PGA, 1867”) is recognized as the primary legality driving the prevalence of gambling in India.
 However, the fantasy sports games are considered to be an exception under the PGA wherein the provisions and punishments of PGA shall not be applicable to games played by the user using their skills and knowledge as primary tools.

UNCLEARED AREAS IN INDIA TO PLAY- FANTASY
There are various states in India wherein the laws related to the game of skills are unclear. In this regard, for the websites offering fantasy sports it remains unclear whether to offer the services for free or not. The Indian states with no clearance regarding the offering of pay-to-play contests include Assam, Odisha, Telangana and Nagaland.
In this context, Rising11 does not permits the users identified as the residents of Odisha, Telangana, Assam and Nagaland to participate in the pay-to-play contest(s) organized by Rising11.


</string>


    <string name="about_us"> Rising11 is a most promising &amp; growing Fantasy Platform in India, where Sports are not only sports- it’s more than a religion for peoples. Where the peoples are come to stadium &amp; also watch the matches In-Front-Of TV for entertainment and support Their Teams and favourite players as only spectators.
        But in this modern Era where peoples are watching matches only as a spectator on the other side Rising 11 offers a very exciting &amp; promising game to peoples from all across the India to make their dreams come true to play on Rising11 by creating their Teams and win real money by join the contests on fantasy platform from real time live matches in multiple sports (CRICKET, FOOTBALL, KABADDI etc.).
        So now stop to watch only, it’s time to playing on Rising11 and become a Rising Hero of your own life &amp; world.
        Vision-
        Our vision to establish the Rising11 is to give a most promising, superior and Trustable fantasy platform to user for showing his/her skills &amp; knowledge and live him/her dreams in real life. And we also want that the every sports lover will enable their control on their own team &amp; show their skills.
        Mission- (t-3)
        Rising11 wants to make a new world of Fantasy Sports Gaming where every user think that they are not less than a real life player and they have got the skills that make them to a RISING HERO of the world.
        We want to make a different level of Fantasy gaming to offer the Best Fantasy Services in multiple sports. To reach the Heights we planned to achieve, we working extraordinary and walking to a path of Truth-Trust-Transparency.</string>


    <string name="FAQs"></string>


    <string name="account_balance">You can view, withdraw or deposit money into your Rising11 account anytime by going to the “My Account” link.
        You will need to go through a One Time Account Verification process before you withdraw any money from your Rising11 account. Don’t worry – this process wont take time and will not be repeated unless you change any of your details.
        Money in your Rising11 account is divided into 3 categories:
        Unutilized: If you have deposited any amount but have not yet joined any league using this amount, it will be categorized as Unutilized in your Rising11 account.
        Winnings: The amount of money earned as “winnings” through any cash leagues joined. No processing fees will be deducted if you wish to withdraw any amount from your Winnings!
        Cash Bonus: It’s on us! This is a bonus amount given by Rising11 to you. This amount cannot be withdrawn, however it can be used to join any public cash leagues and win more cash! This cash bonus comes with an expiry date so make full use of this freebie and get started!</string>


    <string name="manage_team">You can make changes to your Rising11 teams as you like until the deadline of the match that you selected !
        You can also change your Captain or Vice Captain before the deadline of the match. Select the “Edit Team” button to make changes to your team.
        Make sure you keep an eye on which of your players are playing the match and keep your session updated at all times.</string>


    <string name="introduction">Rising11 is India’s most promising Sports Game with its Best Functionality &amp; user Friendly solutions.
        Rising11 is played by using your sport knowledge and skills. You can pick your own team made up of real players for Cricket, Football &amp; Kabaddi. Create your team within a maximum budget of 100 credits. Your team earns points based on your chosen players performance in the real-life matches. Its time to showcase your skill and go to become a Rising Hero !
        Follow these 6 easy steps to get started:-
        Select the Sports:
        Select the sport for which you want to play and join contests.
        Select A Match:
        Select any of the upcoming matches from any of the current or upcoming  series or Tournaments (Leagues).
        Create Your Team:
        Use your sports knowledge and showcase your skills to create your Rising11 team within a budget of 100 credits
        Join a Contest:
        Join any Rising11 free or cash contest to win cash and the ultimate bragging rights to showoff your improvement in the Free/Skill contests on Rising11!
        Follow the Match:
        Watch the real match and track your fantasy scorecard in live match.
        Withdraw your Winnings:
        Withdraw your winnings instantly from your Rising11 account (One Time Verification required).</string>


</resources>
