<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rising 11</string>
    <string name="title_activity_create_contest">CREATE A CONTEST</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">RISING 11</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_notification">Notification</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="title_activity_temp">TempActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="underline_string"><u>Know more</u></string>
    <string name="line1_bullet">\u2022 Track the status of withdrawals</string>
    <string name="line2_bullet">\u2022 Enjoy access to exciting features &amp; rewards</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <!-- API URLs -->
    <string name="paytm_mid">YfSFky58226330996541</string>
    <string name="generate_checksum_url">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/paytm/generateChecksum.php</string>
    <string name="callback_url">https://pguat.paytm.com/paytmchecksum/paytmCallback.jsp</string>

    <!-- apis-->
    <string name="signup">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/register-user.php</string>
    <string name="signin">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/login.php</string>
    <string name="forgetpass">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/forget-pass.php</string>
    <string name="update_profile">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/update-profile.php</string>

    <string name="verifymobile">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/verify-mobile.php</string>
    <string name="userdetails">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/get-user-details.php</string>
    <string name="wallet">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/get-wallet-balance.php</string>
    <string name="create_contest">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/create-contest.php</string>
    <string name="add_contets_prize">http://rising11.com/apps/apis/add-contest-prize.php</string>


    <string name="how_it_works_step">Step-1:- Verify your email &amp; mobile no.\n\nStep-2:-Refer your Friend <b>Rising11</b> by unique referral code.
        \n\nStep-3:-When your Friend Register and Verify their email &amp; mobile no. , your friend will get ₹50 instantly and you will get ₹15 cash bonus instantly.
        \n\nStep-4:-when your Friend Verify their pan-card &amp; Bank-account further you will get ₹10 cash bonus.</string>

    <string name="how_it_works_button">***If any user will found to miss-use of cash bonus by creating multiple accounts &amp; verify them by fake documents then it will be considered under fair-play violation.
        \n\n*Please refer Terms &amp; Conditions (Refer &amp; Earn) and Fair-Play Violation.</string>

    <string name="fair_play_rules_top">What are the rules of FairPlay?</string>
    <string name="fair_play_rules_middle">• You cannot create multipe account.
        \n\n• You cannot misuse your invite code in any way.
         \n\n• You cannot misuse your cash bonus in any way.
         \n \n\nWhat happens when:
          \n\n• You misuse your Invite Code by creating multiple account:
         \n\n<b> WE BLOCK THE CASH BONUS AND THE INVITE CODE</b>
         \n\n• You misuse the cash bonus and win multiple contests:
         \n\n<b>WE TAKE BACK WINNING OF THAT CONTEST</b>
    </string>

    <string name="fair_play_TC_1">Rising11 considers Fair Play to be a priority at its platform and any user violating the Fair Play Terms of Rising11 shall be entitled to bear various consequences including Blocking of the user Account.</string>

    <string name="fair_play_TC_2">• The people you are referring should all be genuine accounts and the user should not use any fake accounts to gain the “Refer &amp; Earn” cash bonus amount.
        \n\n• The PAN card of all your referred friends should be verified. In an event, the PAN card of more than 3 of your referred friends are not verified the user will be considered as violating the Fair Play Terms of Rising11.
        \n\n• A user creating more than one account on Rising11 platform will be considered as violating the Fair Play Terms of Rising11 as Rising11 neither allows nor encourages any user to create more than one user account on Rising11.
        \n\n• Withdrawing money by using any unlawful or illegal means or trying to withdraw money by illegal manners is considered as Fair Play violation at Rising11.
        \n\n• If a user is found submitting fake copies or someone else’s documents while registering with Rising11, the act will be considered as violating the Fair Play Terms of Rising11.
        \n\n• In case a user is found to be creating and using multiple accounts on a single device amid regular platform audits, then, the case shall be considered to violate Fair Play Terms of Rising11 and shall attract needed actions. As part of the action, the withdrawal request of the user shall be put on hold.</string>

    <string name="fair_play_TC_3">\n\n• As a part of consequences for violating the terms of Fair Play at Rising11, the account of the user found to be violating the Fair Play terms will be blocked.
        \n\n• Further, in other scenario the total amount present in the Rising11 wallet of the user violating the Fair Play terms of Rising11 will be reduced to zero.</string>


    <!-- CRIC_API -->

    <string name="Cric_APi_Key">1FiCfYXHgZPywU2JFPgdnPL7NX63</string>
    <string name="Cric_cricket_score">https://cricapi.com/api/cricketScore</string>


    <string-array name="sort_by_value">
        <item>Player Type</item>
        <item>Points</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- More Section Data -->

    <string name="help_section_1">For any queries please write email to us on- \n<b>support@rising11.com</b> \n<b>info@rising11.com</b>
        \n\nYou can also message us on WhatsApp at -  <b>7023083083</b>
    </string>

    <string name="fb">https://www.facebook.com/Rising11kk/?ti=as</string>
    <string name="insta">https://www.instagram.com/rising11kk</string>
    <string name="twitter">https://twitter.com/Rising11_kk?s=08</string>
    <string name="youtube">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCMWcWW4oLaTOZGDo1enSpHg</string>


    <string name="jobs">Thanks for being interested to know about us. Well, we are a bunch of Sports lovers who want to present other Sports lovers an experience like never before. We worked day in and day out to come up with this delightful experience of Sports matches. Hence, we would like to invite you to be a part of our fastest growing &amp; promising family
        \n\nCongratulations! We’re now open to invite more members to join our fantasy family.
        \n\nSend your resume to us at - <b>info@rising11.com</b>
        \n\n<b>We look forward to joining hands with you!</b> </string>


    <string name="legality_part_1"> Fantasy sports are considered to be a legal practice around the world with certain states being an exception. The fantasy sports are entirely based on the concept of Game of Skills, wherein the users form their own teams and are allocated points on the basis of on-field performance of their chosen players.
        \n\nThe services and Fun Features offered by Rising11 are all a game of skills and do not promote, encourage or support gambling or betting in any manner. The game of skills can be defined as a game wherein the skills of the individuals participating in any online fantasy game play a dominant role rather than the mere luck of the individuals. The individuals in game of skills use their skills, knowledge, training and attention for participation and winning.
        \n\nRising11 is completely legal as it offers services, Fun Features, Program(s) and Contest(s) related to fantasy sports. The services, contest(s) and program(s) related to fantasy sports offered by Rising11 enables its users to create their own team of playing XI prior the match begins and then the teams are awarded points on the basis of the real life performance of the players chosen by the users in their playing XI. The individual whose team scores the highest aggregate of points is announced as the winners. The formation of team by the users of Rising11 is entirely dependent on the skills, knowledge and attention of the users which makes the fantasy sports offered at Rising11 a game of skills and 100% legal.
    </string>

    <string name="legality_part_2">The game of skills such as the fantasy sports gamings are considered to be legal all over India expect certain states such as Assam, Odisha, Telangana and Nagaland.
        \n\nThe PGA defines the act of “public gambling” and keeping of a common gaming house as a criminal and punishable act in India. The Public Gambling Act, 1867 (“PGA, 1867”) is recognized as the primary legality driving the prevalence of gambling in India.
        \n\nHowever, the fantasy sports games are considered to be an exception under the PGA wherein the provisions and punishments of PGA shall not be applicable to games played by the user using their skills and knowledge as primary tools.
    </string>

    <string name="legality_part_3">There are various states in India wherein the laws related to the game of skills are unclear. In this regard, for the websites offering fantasy sports it remains unclear whether to offer the services for free or not. The Indian states with no clearance regarding the offering of pay-to-play contests include Assam, Odisha, Telangana and Nagaland.
        \n\nIn this context, Rising11 does not permits the users identified as the residents of Odisha, Telangana, Assam and Nagaland to participate in the pay-to-play contest(s) organized by Rising11.
</string>


    <string name="about_us_1"><b>Rising11</b> is a most promising &amp; growing Fantasy Platform in India, where Sports are not only sports- it’s more than a religion for peoples. Where the peoples are come to stadium &amp; also watch the matches In-Front-Of TV for entertainment and support Their Teams and favourite players as only spectators.
        \n\nBut in this modern Era where peoples are watching matches only as a spectator on the other side Rising 11 offers a very exciting &amp; promising game to peoples from all across the India to make their dreams come true to play on Rising11 by creating their Teams and win real money by join the contests on fantasy platform from real time live matches in multiple sports (CRICKET, FOOTBALL, KABADDI etc.).
        \n\nSo now stop to watch only, it’s time to playing on Rising11 and become a Rising Hero of your own life &amp; world.
    </string>

    <string name="about_us_2">Our vision to establish the Rising11 is to give a most promising, superior and Trustable fantasy platform to user for showing his/her skills &amp; knowledge and live him/her dreams in real life. And we also want that the every sports lover will enable their control on their own team &amp; show their skills.</string>
    <string name="about_us_3"><b>Rising11</b> wants to make a new world of Fantasy Sports Gaming where every user think that they are not less than a real life player and they have got the skills that make them to a <b>RISING HERO</b> of the world.
        \n\nWe want to make a different level of Fantasy gaming to offer the Best Fantasy Services in multiple sports. To reach the Heights we planned to achieve, we working extraordinary and walking to a path of <b>Truth-Trust-Transparency.</b></string>

    <string name="account_balance">You can view, withdraw or deposit money into your Rising11 account anytime by going to the “My Account” link.
        \n\nYou will need to go through a One Time Account Verification process before you withdraw any money from your Rising11 account. Don’t worry – this process wont take time and will not be repeated unless you change any of your details.
        \n\nMoney in your Rising11 account is divided into 3 categories:
        \n\n<b>Unutilized:</b> If you have deposited any amount but have not yet joined any league using this amount, it will be categorized as Unutilized in your Rising11 account.
        \n\n<b>Winnings:</b> The amount of money earned as “winnings” through any cash leagues joined. No processing fees will be deducted if you wish to withdraw any amount from your Winnings!
        \n\n<b>Cash Bonus:</b> It’s on us! This is a bonus amount given by Rising11 to you. This amount cannot be withdrawn, however it can be used to join any public cash leagues and win more cash! This cash bonus comes with an expiry date so make full use of this freebie and get started!</string>


    <string name="manage_team">You can make changes to your Rising11 teams as you like until the deadline of the match that you selected !
        \n\nYou can also change your Captain or Vice Captain before the deadline of the match. Select the “Edit Team” button to make changes to your team.
        \n\nMake sure you keep an eye on which of your players are playing the match and keep your session updated at all times.</string>


    <string name="introduction"><b>Rising11</b> is India’s most promising Sports Game with its Best Functionality &amp; user Friendly solutions.
        \n\n<b>Rising11</b> is played by using your sport knowledge and skills. You can pick your own team made up of real players for Cricket, Football &amp; Kabaddi. Create your team within a maximum budget of 100 credits. Your team earns points based on your chosen players performance in the real-life matches. Its time to showcase your skill and go to become a Rising Hero !
        \n\n<b>Follow these 6 easy steps to get started:-</b>
        \n\n<b>Select the Sports:</b>
        \n\nSelect the sport for which you want to play and join contests.
        \n\n<b>Select A Match:</b>
        \n\nSelect any of the upcoming matches from any of the current or upcoming  series or Tournaments (Leagues).
        \n\n<b>Create Your Team:</b>
        \n\nUse your sports knowledge and showcase your skills to create your Rising11 team within a budget of 100 credits
        \n\n<b>Join a Contest:</b>
        \n\nJoin any Rising11 free or cash contest to win cash and the ultimate bragging rights to showoff your improvement in the Free/Skill contests on Rising11!
        \n\n<b>Follow the Match:</b>
        \n\nWatch the real match and track your fantasy scorecard in live match.
        \n\n<b>Withdraw your Winnings:?</b>
        \n\nWithdraw your winnings instantly from your Rising11 account (One Time Verification required).</string>


    <string name="FAQs">
        \n\nRising11 Account-
\n\nWhat is Rising11?
\n\nRising11 is one of the most promising fantasy sports gaming platform in India with best services. Rising11 offers the users to earn real money by using their skills and knowledge for playing fantasy sports in multiple sports.
\n\nHow do I sign up?
\n\nThe users can sign up on Rising11 by filling a short registration form available on the homepage of Rising11 App.
\n\nWhy can’t I log in to my account?
\n\nThe users may encounter signup problems due to various reasons. The primary reasons due to which the user might not be able to signup can include the user might be entering incorrect email address or password. In case the user has forgotten his/her password, there’s a Forgot Password link available below the login option. By clicking on the Forgot Password link, the user will be taken to a new webpage, wherein the user can reset his/her password by entering his/her registered mobile number and Rising11 will send an OTP. The user can enter the OTP sent by Rising11 to reset his/her password.
\n\nCan I have multiple accounts on Rising11?
\n\nNo,A user is permitted to have only one account under its name with valid supporting documents on Rising11. Please refer Fair Play policy for further details.
\n\nCan I update/edit my information?
\n\nThe users can easily update/edit their information by logging into their Rising11 account using their registered email address and password .After logging into their Rising11 account the user can edit/update their information by clicking on ‘My info &amp; setting’ on the top left of the page. The users will be able to edit their basic information including date of birth and address but the user won’t be allowed to change, update/edit their profile name, email address, mobile number or team name once registered with Rising11.
\n\nI’m sure I’ve got the right username and password but I still can’t log in.
\n\nIn case you are a registered and verified user of Rising11, and are using the correct registered email address and mobile number but still can’t login into your Rising11 account, please reach out to us via the Contact Us page.
\n\nI did not get any confirmation email after I signed up.
\n\nIn case you haven’t received any confirmation email from Rising11 after registering with Rising11 there could be 2 reasons:
\n\n1.-The mail sent by Rising11 might have been marked as “Spam” and could have been sent to the spam folder of your mailbox. In such case, please check the spam folder of your mailbox and mark Rising11 as ‘Not Spam,’ additionally add Rising11 to your contacts in order to avoid any future inconvenience.
\n\n2.-The user might have mistyped his/her email address while registering with Rising11. In such case, please reach out to us via our Contact Us page
\n\nI don’t know much about Fantasy sports – can I still play?
\n\nSo, yes, you can play even if you don’t know much about fantasy. The fantasy sports services offered by Rising11 are for everyone including those who don’t know much about cricket. In addition, the “How to Play” section of Rising11 website can assist you in playing the game by briefing you about the playing tactics.
\n\nPlaying on Rising11-
\n\nHow do I play on Rising11?
\n\nThe users can avail the services offered by Rising11 and play contest(s) organized on Rising11 by simply registering/logging into their account. In order to play and avail the services provided, the user needs to follow these simple steps:
\n\n1.	Register/Login to Rising11
\n\n2.	Select the match you want to join and then click on the ‘Create New Team’ button for creating your team
\n\n3.	Create your team of players (including a Captain &amp; Vice-captain) within an allocated virtual budget of 100 credit points choosing from all the players in the match for every sports.
\n\n4.	Join free or cash contests of your choice. Cash contests let you win cash and require an entry fee, for which we provide multiple payment methods such as Credit Cards, Debit Cards, Net banking, and different wallet services.
\n\n5.	After the beginning of the match your team is awarded points on the basis of the on-field performance of your selected players. Final points, ranks, and winners are declared after the end of the match
\n\nWhen does Fantasy Games start on Rising11?
\n\nFantasy games on Rising11 are comes with a deadline which is usually prior 5 minutes before the beginning of the real match.
\n\n
\n\nHow do I select my team?
\n\nCreating a team on Rising11 is very Simple, the user can create his/her team by selecting the match. He/she wants to join and then clicking on the “Create New Team” option available under “My Teams” section. The user can then create his/her team by selecting 11 players (including Captain and Vice-Captain) in fantasy cricket &amp; fantasy football, 7 players (including Captain and Vice-Captain) in fantasy kabaddi, from the individuals playing in the match within the given virtual budget of 100 credit points.
\n\n
\n\nCan I change my teams for future matches?
\n\nYes, the user needs to create a new team for every match on Rising11.
\n\n
\n\nWhat if one of my chosen players does not play in the match?
\n\nIn a match if your chosen player is not playing, then your team will not be awarded any points.
\n\n
\n\nHow many players are needed to create a team?
\n\nIn order to create a team, the user requires 11 players in cricket wherein there must be at least 3 bowlers, 3 batsmen, 1 all-rounder &amp; 1 wicket-keeper, 11 players in football where there should be at least 3 defenders, 3 mid-fielders, 1 striker &amp; 1 goal-keeper, 7 in kabaddi with at least 2 defenders, 1 all-rounder &amp; 1 raider.
\n\nCan I choose players from one side only?
\n\nNo, the users cannot choose players from one team only. They are allowed to choose a maximum of 7 players only from a single team in cricket &amp; football, and a maximum of 4 players in kabaddi. The remaining players should be selected from the other side.
\n\n
\n\nI’ve spent my entire budget before selecting all the players of my fantasy team. How do I complete my team?
\n\nRising11 allows the users to create their team within a virtual budget of 100 credit points only. Thus, the user must use the provided credits efficiently for selecting all the players of the team within the given budget of 100 credit points only.
\n\n
\n\nWhat is the use of a Captain &amp; Vice-captain in a team?
      \n\n  The player chosen as the Captain of the user’s team is awarded 2 times the original points whereas the Vice-captain of the team is awarded 1.5 times the original points according to their on-field performance.
\n\nWhen I make changes to my team, how long does it take for the changes to reflect?
\n\nThe users are allowed to make multiple changes in their team but prior the deadline of the match. In addition, the changes made by the users are modified and reflected instantly.
\n\n
\n\nCan I edit my team during the match?
\n\nThe users are not allowed to create or edit their teams during the match. The users are only allowed to make all the changes prior to the deadline, which is usually 5 minutes before the start time of the real match for every Sport.
\n\nHow can I change my team name?
\n\nRising11 does not allow the users to change their team names once it has been registered with us.
\n\n
\n\nHow do I create multiple teams for the same match?
\n\nThe users can create multiple teams only after creating their first team. The users can create another team by clicking on “Create New Team” option. The user can additionally create a new team by cloning his/her previous team via the “Clone” option available on the My Teams page.
\n\n
\n\nHow many teams can I create for a single match?
\n\nRising11 allows the users to create a maximum of 5 teams for a single match.
\n\n
\n\nCan I join the same contest using multiple teams?
\n\nIn an event wherein the contest displays “Multiple Entry,” a user can join the same contest using a maximum of 5 teams otherwise the user is allowed to join one contest with one team only. The user can identify a “Multiple Entry” contest through an “M” sign embarked on the contest.
\n\n
\n\nCan I choose which of my teams will compete in a contest (Team 1/ Team 2/Team3) after joining?
\n\nThe users are allowed to choose their team in a contest (Choose Team 1/Team 2/Team3  to compete) from the ‘Joined contests’ tab until the deadline.
\n\n
\n\nScores and Points-
\n\nHow will my Team score points?
\n\nThe user’s teams are awarded scores on the basis of the on-field performance of their selected players in the live match. Check out our ‘Fantasy Points System’ to know more about the points.
\n\n
\n\nWhen do the points get updated?
\n\nThe points usually get updated in every few minutes, however, the final points, team’s total and your rank are calculated and updated after the completion of the match. The declaration of winners and distribution of prizes is accomplished only after the point verification on the part of Rising11.
\n\n
\n\nI have created my team before the deadline, so why hasn’t my team got any points yet?
\n\nThe points are awarded to the users on the basis of on-field performance of their selected players. Thus, the points are awarded only after the beginning of the live match.
\n\n
\n\nWhich website do you refer to update the points?
\n\nThe scores are calculated on the basis of information received from third-party sources. The third-party sources associated with Rising11 are completely reliable such as governing bodies, to correct and verify the score feed &amp; ensure accurate tabulation of points. In addition, the scores are calculated on the basis of the live feed of the matches.
\n\n
\n\nWill I get points for Man of the Match?
\n\nNo, there are no points awarded for Man of the Match.
\n\n
\n\nWhat happens when there is a tie between users? How will you distribute the prize?
\n\nIn an event wherein there’s a tie between two or more users the prize money is distributed between the users equally.
\n\n
\n\nDo I get points for a Super Over in a Match?
\n\nNo, points are not awarded to the users for a super over in a match as the points scored or wickets taken by the players in a super over are not considered in their official records.
\n\n
\n\nHow can I cross check my team’s points?
\n\nThe users can cross-check their team’s points by clicking on the ‘Fantasy Scorecard’ link on the Live Score page. If you want to cross check your team’s points with the points system again, visit our ‘Fantasy Points System’ page.
\n\n
\n\nIf a player is sent off by the umpires for misconduct in a match, does he still score points on Rising11 once he’s back on the field?
\n\nIn an event where in any player is sent off the field in a match by the umpire, the player will still score and retain points on Rising11 according to the standard point system of Rising11 for his performance and contribution on the field. Further, if the umpires allow the player to get back on the field in the same match, the player will once again be eligible to score points for the duration of his stay on the field.
\n\n
\n\nDo I get points for a substitute player if replaces any player on-field?
\n\nNo, your team is not awarded any points for a substitute player in case he replaces any player on-field as the substitute is not considered as a part of playing XI in cricket &amp; football. However, in kabaddi, 2 points are awarded to the substitute player.
\n\n
\n\nContests-
\n\nWhat type of contests can I join?
\n\nThe users using the services and Fun Features provided by Rising11 can join various types of contests organized by Rising11 such as 5-members, 10-members, 30-members and 100-members contests (depending on the number of competitors in a contest). Further, the users can join cash contest(s) to win real money or they can join the practice contests free of cost to enhance their playing skills.
\n\n
\n\nWhat are public contests?
\n\nThe public contests organized by Rising11 are contests that are open to everyone. Any of the Rising11 users can join the public contest(s) organized by Rising11 and be eligible for winning the contest(s).
\n\n
\n\nWhat are private contests?
\n\nThe private contests organized on Rising11 are contests which the user creates. In private contest a user can create his/her own contest with a pre-defined number of participants and a pre-defined winnings amount. The private contest can be shared by the user among his/her friends via a unique code. As the private contests are the contests created by the user, thus, it is not visible to all the users of Rising11 and is only accessible by the users who have the unique code for the contest.
\n\n
\n\nHow do I join contests?
\n\nThe users can easily join any of the contests organized by Rising11 by just clicking on the ‘Join‘ button below the specific contest, the user wishes to join.
\n\n
\n\nWhat are cash contests?
\n\nThe cash contests organized by Rising11 are contests wherein the users can join by paying a pre-defined entry fee and can compete with other Rising11 users in order to win prizes and real money. However, the user whose team scores the highest aggregate of points will be declared as the winner of the contest.
\n\n
\n\nHow do I know if a contest has a single winner or more than one winner?
\n\nThe users can identify if a contest has a single winner or more than one winner by selecting the contest and clicking on the Winners option to view a detailed list of winners &amp; the prize money for each rank.
\n\n
\n\nHow many winners will be announced for contests with multiple winners?
\n\nThe number of winners in the contest(s) organized by Rising11 varies from one contest to the other. The number of winners to be declared in a contest will be disclosed to the users as soon as the contest is made available to join.
\n\n
\n\nHow is the prize money distributed in case of multiple winners?
\n\nThe users can check the distribution of prize money in case of “Multiple Winners” by clicking on the pre-defined number of winners below each of the contests. In an event, the winning amount is more than ₹10,000, there will be tax deductions according to the government taxation policies. The tax deduction in case of winnings worth more than ₹10,000 is done in case of single winning of the user with a single team. In case the user wins more than ₹10,000 with multiple teams then no deductions will be made.
\n\n
\n\nWhat happens if there is a tie between winners of a multiple winner contests?
\n\nIn an event wherein there is a tie between winners of a multiple winner contests, the prize money for the position of the winners and the immediately next winning position (if any), and so forth complying with the number of tied winners, will be summed up and then distributed equally among the tied winners. All other prize money will remain as per the winner’s standing.
\n\nFor instance: In an event wherein there are 2 tied winners of a multiple winner contests for the 1st position in the contest, then the prize money of the 1st and 2nd position will be summed up and then distributed among the 2 tied winners. Further, the next highest scoring individual will be awarded the prize money for the 3rd position.
\n\n
\n\nWhat happens if an ODI/T20 match is abandoned?
\n\nIn an event wherein an ODI/T20 is called-off, the fantasy cricket contest(s) organized on Rising11 associated with the real match will be cancelled and the entry fees will be refunded to the users. This comprises of both the circumstances wherein the real match is abandoned either without a single ball being bowled, or the match is abandoned after it has begun.
\n\n
\n\nWhat happens if a test match is declared as drawn?
\n\nIn an event wherein the real test match is announced as drawn with neither of the teams completing a single inning, the fantasy match will be cancelled and the entry fees will be refunded to the users.
\n\nFurther, in an event wherein the real match is declared as drawn with either of the teams completing an inning, the fantasy match will be considered to have completed and the entry fees will not be refunded.
\n\n
\n\nWhat happens when a match is completed as per the D/L method?
\n\nIn an event any match is completed through D/L method, the match is considered as completed on Rising11 and the points are awarded accordingly. In such cases, the ranks and points are awarded on the basis of live scores and no refund is made in such cases.
\n\n
\n\nWhat if the contest doesn’t fill up with the required number of participants?
\n\nIn this condition, it will also Mentioned in contest details.
\n\nWhat do I win in a cash contest?
\n\nThe users playing the cash contest(s) organized by Rising11 win real money according to his/her rank as the winning prize.
\n\n
\n\nWhy do ranks keep fluctuating during a contest?
\n\nThe ranks keep fluctuating in a mid of contest because of the changes in the aggregate scores of the teams due to the on-field performance of your chosen players.
\n\n
\n\nCan I join a contest in the middle of the series?
\n\nYes, the users can join a contest in the middle of a series in an event that the series is not yet closed i.e. it has not reached its deadline. Further, users joining a contest in the middle of the series have an equal opportunity of winning as everyone else.
\n\n
\n\nHow do you decide the winner of a contest?
\n\nThe winner in a contest is decided on the basis of the aggregate a team scores. The user whose team scores the highest aggregate of scores on the basis of the on-field performance of their chosen players is announced as the winner of a contest.
\n\n
\n\nCash Prizes-
\n\nHow will I be informed if I win a Cash prize?
\n\nRising11 updates the final ranks and points immediately at the end of every match. In an event a user wins a cash prize post participating in a contest(s), the winnings amount will be credited automatically to the Rising11 account wallet of the user.
\n\n
\n\nWhen will the winnings be distributed?
\n\nRising11 usually completes the process of winner declaration and distribution of winnings amount among the winners within few hours after the end of the match. Rising11 team checks and verifies the scorecard of the live match with the scorecard at Rising11 in order to ensure that correct points have been rewarded to the users on the basis of on-field performance of their chosen players.
\n\n
\n\nDoes the amount in my Winnings Account have any expiry date?
\n\nThe amount in the winnings account of the user should be withdrawn to the user’s bank account within 365 days of the transfer. In an event the user fails to withdraw his/her winnings within 365 days of credit, then the winnings amount of the user will be forfeited by Rising11.
\n\n
\n\nAccount Balance-
\n\nHow do I check my Rising11 account balance?
\n\nThe users can check their Rising11 account balance by clicking at the Menu option available at the top left corner of their screen. After clicking on the Menu option click on the My Account section for a detailed account balance and most recent transactions on Rising11.
\n\n
\n\nWhat are the ways to add money?
\n\nThe users can add money to their Rising11 account by using various transaction methods such as Debit Card, Credit Card, Net banking and different wallets. If the users have any query regarding adding money to their Rising11 wallet they can reach out to us via our Contact Us page.
\n\n
\n\nIs it safe to pay through your application?
\n\nRising11 uses verified third-party payment gateways that use various security checks in order to ensure that all the transactions on our website are completely safe and credible.
\n\n
\n\nHow do I get through the payment gateway?
\n\nYou don’t need to do anything special; we’ll take care of this during the payment process. &amp; ensure you have a hassle-free experience.
\n\n
\n\nHow do I get notification for my transaction?
\n\nRising11 sends you a confirmation email to your registered email address submitted at the time of registering with Rising11 along with an Order No. or a Transaction Id of your transaction.
\n\n
\n\nWhat if the payment is deducted from my card and not updated in the Rising11 account?
\n\nThis usually happens when there is a delay in communication among the parties involved in the transaction primarily from the bank’s end. In such an event the users can reach out to us via our Contact Us page with the screenshot of their card/bank statement affirming that there has been a deduction from the user’s card so that we can check and assist the users with their concerns and queries.
\n\n
\n\nHow long does it take for my deposited amount to be credited into my Rising11 account balance?
\n\nThe account balance of your Rising11 will be updated immediately after you have made a deposit to your account. In case the balance in your Rising11 account is not updated immediately reach out to us via our Contact Us page.
\n\n
\n\nDoes the amount in my ‘Unutilized’ Account have any expiry date?
\n\nYes, the amount deposited in your unutilized accounts comes with an expiry date and should be used within 365 days of credit. In an event, the user does not use the amount deposited in their unutilized amount within 365 days from the date of credit Rising11 is authorized to forfeit such unutilized amount, without any liability or obligation to pay any compensation to you.
\n\n
\n\nIn what order does my Account Balance get utilized towards the entry fee for a cash contest?
\n\nRising11, first of all, deducts the amount from your unutilized account followed by your Cash Bonus account, and lastly from your Winnings account to cover the entry fee for any cash contest that you join.
\n\n
\n\nWhat is Cash Bonus? How can I get it?
\n\nThe cash bonus offered by Rising11 can be defined as an amount awarded to the users by Rising11 under various schemes and promotions of Rising11. In addition, the users can receive a cash bonus when they join Rising11 for the first time or under promotional schemes of Rising11.
\n\n
\n\nWhat if my transaction fails and the amount is deducted from my bank account?
\n\nIn case you are carrying out a transaction on Rising11 and your transaction fails due to certain circumstances and the amount is deducted from your bank account but is not added to your Rising11 account. In such case please contact the payment gateway you had used for carrying out the transaction. The transaction failure amounts are to be refunded by the payment gateways as we do not receive any payments in case of transaction failure.
\n\n
\n\nDoes the Sign-up bonus in my wallet have with an Expiry Date?
\n\nSign-up bonus credited to your Rising11 wallet while joining the platform will expire within 30 days of the credit of the amount.
\n\n
\n\nDoes my Transaction history have a Validity?
\n\nAll your Transaction history (including but not limited to Amount Added, Winnings, League Joined, etc.) will only be available for the last 15 days. In case you’ve any query related to any of your transaction please reach our support team within 7 days of occurrence of the issue.
\n\n
\n\nVerification-
\n\nIs verification necessary to join contests on Rising11?
\n\nIn order to join contests on Rising11, the users are required to verify at least their email address and mobile number. However, the user will not be eligible for the cash bonus offered by Rising11 to its new users. In addition, the user would not be allowed for any withdrawal until and unless his/her account is verified by Rising11.
\n\n
\n\nHow do I get my Rising11 account verified?
\n\nThe account verification process with Rising11 is very simple and a one-time process. In order to verify your account manually click on the Menu button available at the top left corner of the page and then select “Verify” from the drop-down menu. Verify your account by following the below-mentioned steps:
\n\n1.	Enter your mobile number and then enter the OTP received on the mobile number in order to verify your mobile number.
\n\n2.	Enter your email address and verify your email address by clicking the verification link sent by Rising11. In an event you have chosen direct registration by logging in with your email address will be automatically verified by Rising11.
\n\n3.	The third step of verification process at Rising11 is the PAN card verification. In order to successfully verify your PAN card details, upload your PAN Card number, PAN Card image and other required details. After successfully uploading and entering the required details click on ‘Save PAN Card”
\n\n4.	After successfully submitting your PAN card details submit your bank account details for completing the verification process. PAN card and bank account details are verified on the very same day.
\n\nNote: The Name on the PAN card and the image proof uploaded as required for Bank Account verification should match with each other. In addition to this, only original image of the PAN card is acceptable, we do not accept photocopies of PAN card for verification.
\n\n
\n\nWhy do I need a PAN card on Rising11?
\n\nRising11 is a fantasy sports platform that enables its users to win real money by using their cricketing skills and knowledge. Rising11 involves transaction and transfer of real money between your Rising11 account and your bank account. Thus, in order to make withdrawals from your Rising11 account, it is mandatory to verify your PAN Card details with Rising11 as a proof of identity. In an event the user does not have a PAN Card, he/she can still play on Rising11 and the winning amounts will be deposited in the “Your Winnings” section of users’ Rising11 wallet. Further, the user can withdraw the amount by applying for a PAN card in the meantime and verifying his/her PAN card details with Rising11.
\n\n
\n\nWhy did my verification fail?
\n\nYour account verification with Rising11 can fail because of many reasons which might include:
\n\n1.	You have not uploaded your PAN Card as an identity proof mandatorily required for verification
\n\n2.	The PAN card number entered by you does not match with the PAN card details submitted at the time of verification request.
\n\n3.	The Date of Birth entered by you at the time of creating your Rising11 account does not match with the Date of Birth mentioned on the PAN Card submitted by you.
\n\n4.	Your name on the PAN card and on the bank account does not match.
\n\n5.	The IFSC code you have provided is either incorrect or does not belong to the bank branch mentioned for verification.
\n\n6.	The visibility or clarity factor of the documents uploaded by you is very low.
\n\n7.	The bank account number on the bank account proof uploaded by you for verification purpose does not match with the Bank account number entered by you in the verification request.
\n\nIn an event, if your verification request gets rejected and your verification fails you will be informed about the reason leading to verification failure which will be appearing on top of the verification page for your reference.
\n\n
\n\nWithdrawals-
\n\nHow do I withdraw money from my Rising11 account?
\n\nThe users are allowed to withdraw money from “My Winnings” section of their Rising11 wallet, only after they successfully complete the verification process. The users can withdraw a minimum of ₹200 and a maximum of ₹50,000 in a day wherein the user can make a request of ₹25,000 at a time. Further, the withdrawal amount will be deposited to your bank accounts within a time period of 2-3 days.
\n\n
\n\nWhy can’t I withdraw the Cash Bonus available in my Rising11 account?
\n\nThe cash bonus is an amount provided to you by Rising11 under various schemes additionally it comes with an expiry date. Thus, you cannot withdraw the cash bonus amount in Rising11 but you can use the bonus provided as a part of offers to pay of the entry fee to join contests. However, the bonus provided as a part of Refer &amp; Earn program can be used to pay the entry fee to join leagues .The bonus amount (if any) shall expire at the end of 30 days from the date of credit of the bonus amount (if any).
\n\n
\n\nWhat bank account details do I need to provide for withdrawal/verification?
\n\nIn order to successfully complete the withdrawal process, the user needs to provide certain information as a part of identity verification. The user needs to provide the following bank account details:
\n\n1.	Name of the bank
\n\n2.	Name of the branch
\n\n3.	Name of the account holder
\n\n4.	Account Number
\n\n5.	IFSC code
\n\n
\n\nLegality-
\n\nIs the paid version of Fantasy Games legal in India?
\n\nYes, the paid version of Fantasy Games is legal in India as it is considered to be a game of skills which is legal.
\n\n
\n\nAm I allowed to play if I’m under the age of 18?
\n\nRising11 does not allow any individual below the age of 18 to participate or use the services and Fun Features provided by Rising11.
\n\n
\n\nDo I have to pay taxes when I withdraw money to my bank account?
\n\nIn an event, the Winning amount crosses the mark of ₹10,000 a tax of 31.20% is imposed on the amount which is paid off by Rising11 by deducting the tax amount from the winning amount. However, the users are provided TDS certificates in accordance to the Income Tax Act 1961. In addition, the users shall be responsible for payment of any other applicable tax, including (but not limited to), income tax, gift tax, etc. in respect of the Cash Prizes money won.
\n\n
\n\nFair Play Violation-
\n\nWhat are the things that are neither allowed not appreciated by the Rising11 platform?
\n\n1.	A single user cannot create multiple accounts on Rising11
\n\n2.	Any user misusing his/her referral code by creating different fake accounts on Rising11 in order to earn Cash Bonus.
\n\n3.	A user is not allowed to submit fake or some else’s documents.
\n\n
\n\nWhat happens if a single user uses various ids or create multiple accounts using his/her referral code in order to earn cash bonus?
\n\nIn case, a user is using a single device for creating multiple accounts on Rising11, it should be ensured by the user that all the mandatory verification formalities including mobile, email, PAN card &amp; Bank Account details verification has been done by the user for all the accounts created. Abiding by the said process will help such users, who create multiple accounts on a single device, in terms of smooth withdrawals on Rising11.
\n\n
\n\nWhat happens if someone converts or tries to convert cash bonus into winnings amount by activities that violate Fair-Play policy of Rising11?
\n\nIn an event any user carries out activities that violate the Fair Play Policies of Rising11 for converting cash bonus into winnings, Rising11 shall block the user refraining him from using the services &amp; Fun Features provided by Rising11 alongside resetting the Rising11 wallet value of the user to “0” by deducting all the amount present in his/her Rising11 wallet.
\n\n
\n\nPayments-
\n\nHow to add a credit/debit card to my Rising11 account?
\n\nYou can add a credit/debit card to your Rising11 account by following a few simple steps. Click on ‘Add Cash’ tab, enter the amount you wish to add and select your payment gateway, select a card and enter your card details. Click on ‘Save &amp; Proceed’
\n\n
\n\nIs it safe to enter my card details? Does Rising11 save any of it?
\n\nRising11 uses secure and credible third-party payment gateways for transactions that use 3D secure authentication which ensures that it is safe to share your card details with Rising11. In addition, Rising11 does not store any of your card information, including your CVV number.
\n\n
\n\nCan I add multiple credit/debit cards to My Account?
\n\nYes, you can add numerous credit/debit cards to your account until and unless they have not expired.
\n\n
\n\nWhat type of cards can be Saved/Used?
\n\nYou can use all major types of credit/debit cards including Visa, MasterCard, Maestro, etc.


    </string>

</resources>
